Hello friends, welcome back to analyzing the
stock market. Today we are going to talk
about ICICI Lombard General Insurance and are going to do its stock analysis
for January 19, 2020-23. Let's go
straight to our chart. Here we have
opened this chart.
I opened this chart with my Zero Tha account.
If you don't have your demat account yet,
I have given the link below in the description of
Zero Tha and Abstract Sridevi. If
you want, you can open
your demat account in stocks through our link
absolutely free and from there you will be
able to start your trading journey. So let's go straight to
our ODI chart. Here, first of all, let's see
what has happened in our stock today. Then
we will go to
our ODI chart. So,
I will talk about closing. Here, our closing was around three dot 93.
Negative
closing exercise at 1200.15. So, is there any possibility of this
in the coming days?
We will discuss whether there is going to be a negative moment or a positive moment. We will also tell you about your
support zone for tomorrow and what is forming in the stock. We will
mark it here daily
and tell you about it. Here, based on today's closing, we will
definitely give our opinion on what we are going to see in the stock tomorrow. So,
let's now go to our ODI chart
and see
what we are going to see in the stock in the coming days.
Here, we have already opened the Van De chart. If
I talk about
high volume, today's
candles are looking like medium to large in size.
I have seen very big candles at the bottom, in a way, it is
also visible. If I talk about
our RSS, it has reached around 38-39,
which gives us a hint of a positive moment here.
But remember, whether it is RSS
or any other indicator, we
cannot rely solely on the indicator. There are
many factors here which
give movement to any stock.
We must consider them
whenever we trade in any stock.  Treat it. Now, as
for my opinion about the stock in the coming days, currently,
my open in the stock here is
definitely a negative moment, whether it is a little
positive, after seeing the negative
moment, we will see it around 12.
I am expecting an upset first of all.
Then after that, in Professor, the stock will
first see green here and
come around 1194. So, you can easily see a downfall in the stock with 117. So,
reduce the stock a little here so that the trend in the stock is
positive right now. In the positive trend,
I would definitely recommend you to
grab the buying side opportunity as much as possible
in Android A because that is where your right to reward ratio will be
in your favor. That is where
you will get the profit ability. What do
you think here,
what can happen in the stock in the coming days, do
tell us by commenting. Here
I will tell you
what levels are being formed in the stock for the short term and long term.
If you want to buy for the short term,
If the stock is above 12:41 for two days, then
you will definitely get an easy gain of
10% from there.
If the moment is low, then if there is a
fast movement, then you will see it within five days.
For the rest,
if in your long term, if you
see the stock coming below level 18, it is a
very good buying level, but at this
level, I would definitely recommend you
that whatever 100% of your capital you want to
invest here in ICICI General
Insurance, you should invest 100% of it at
this level. I will recommend you to invest up to 22-25% of
your capital. Then, if there is a
downfall of 10-20%, then you
can do additional buying there. Additional buying will
help you in reducing your buying average
price here and in the
long term, the lower the average price,
the better the profit you will
see. What do you think about this
or your investment related  If you
need any help, we have given our WhatsApp
number below, you can definitely contact us,
but if you have not subscribed to our channel, then
subscribe to our channel right now, along with that, press the
bell icon, what are you going to see in all the notification stocks of Dhaba, let's
try to understand it completely on the basis of chat, so let's go,
what are we going to see tomorrow,
here we have already opened the chart of Van Hour, all the
supports are already
on silk, so for now
we do not need to mark here, let
me directly talk about its
closing, you can see here,
our closing happened around 1200,
direct support comes at 1196, direct support comes at
1203, remember the
area which is direct from direct support, we
call it no trading area, it means that
if you see the stock moving in this range, then
you have to
not trade here at all, you have to wait for the
stock which is our cross on any one of the two sides and then
conformation Kerala  You have to
take your trade here. If you don't know
what a confirmation candle is, then you must watch the video
I have added on the concept and target
in strategy in the i button.
There
we have explained how you have to see the confirmation candle,
how you have to maintain your target and
stop loss. Also,
whether our stock
is down or going up in intraday,
we have also explained to you how you can make profit in intraday. So,
definitely
watch that video completely. Now, as far as my open is concerned,
before calling it my open,
two important supports are ideal. Here, what is formed after
direct support and director,
I will tell you here. Here, after
direct support, the next support comes at
1190, what happens after that, 1180.
Here, after direct resistance, what is the
next region, 1208, after that,
12-13. So, the two supports that I have
told you here, definitely keep them in consideration for
tomorrow's trade.  Now, as far as the day's trade is concerned, if I talk about tomorrow on the
basis of today's closing in the stock, then my open stock
here is definitely neutral, there is
definitely a closing expectation in the positive side,
but to get neutral,
we will get to see movement around 0.5%
in positive, the rest of the
opening here is a little negative, then there are
chances of seeing the stock coming in the upper side, that
we may see closing in the range of No Trading India, but
because right now the close here is right in the middle, if we
express a little positive then
we will definitely see the stock coming in the range of 1203 to 1208.
What do you think for tomorrow, what can happen tomorrow, do
tell us by commenting and
if you liked our analysis, then
please like and share this video of ours
and do not forget to subscribe to our channel.
Thank you
[Sangeet]